<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>William Burgess - Articles</title>
    <description>A beautiful, fast, Bill
</description>
    <link>
    </link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The sexual convolution</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;The sexual revolution of the 1960s was supposedly an era of free love. But, according to the millenial media, its contemporary equivalent—hookup culture—is decidedly loveless. The two terms describe essentially the same trend of promiscuity (or sexual liberation, to give it an ideological spin). Yet while free love connotes silly, slutty bohemians engaged in harmless rebellion, “hookup culture” shares the same negative space as its evil twin, “rape culture,” or even “consumer culture” and “gun culture.” At face value, such vitriolic phrases are more evocative of bacteria than civil society.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>
        /freelove.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/freelove.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Education &amp; remuneration</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;As university education becomes increasingly commoditized, freshmen inevitably seek out majors with better employment prospects. But unlike most commodities, paying for an education doesn’t guarantee a return. Education is more akin to a gym membership than purchasing a new car, requiring hard work and the right program, in addition to money, to produce a tangible “product.”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>
        /degrees.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/degrees.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Satoshi Nakamoto's cryptic, cryptographic identity</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;“We are all Satoshi.” So claims an email posted to the bitcoin developer mailing list, from an address that—at least at one point—belonged to the enigmatic founder of bitcoin, Satoshi Nakamoto. The email was evidently a response to Australian computer scientist Craig Wright’s announcement that he was Nakamoto, a claim which was immediately disputed and now widely regarded as false. Wright’s evidence was not sufficient. Will the real Satoshi please stand up? And if he does, what would be required from him in order to satisfy skeptics?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>
        /satoshi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/satoshi.html</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>